Jorge Sosa

CONTACTS



Argentina 3400 Corrientes (Corrientes)



(54) 3794 333 171

SOCIAL



https://github.com/jorgegso



https://www.linkedin.com/i n/jorge-sosa-6b47141a6



hajorge2012@gmail.com

SKILL

- . Customer Service
- . Adobe Premiere Pro
- . Photo Editing
- . Git
- . Express
- . Node.js
- . ReactJs
- . HTML
- . UX

PROFILE

Over the time I have acquired a range of skills of all kinds between programming and video editing, customer service and sales I can't spend a day without trying to learn something new. I worked in Argentina and the United States in different fields.

EXPERIENCE

Deer Valley Resort

Party city, Utah U.S Busser (2015 -2016)

Tourism municipality

Argentina, corrientes capital Tourist circuit designer (2017 - 2018)

Hotel Dora

Corrientes, Corrientes Argentina Manager (2010 - 2020)

EDUCATION

Udemy

Web developer react, The complete web developer zero tomastery (2019 - 2020)

Platzi

Introduction to computer security and pentesting (2017 - 2018)

Platzi

Curso de Pentesting 2016 (2016 - 2017)